savesense.com 2015-06-15

# SaveSense

### PRIVACY POLICY

**Last Revised: March 9, 2014**

Welcome to the SaveSense™ downloadable browser add-on application or to our website at the address www.SaveSense.com (collectively and separately known as "SaveSense"), brought to you (the “User", "you") by DealPly Technologies Ltd. ("we", "us", "our", or the "Company"). We respect the privacy of our users and are committed to protect the personal information that users share with us in connection with the use of SaveSense. This Privacy and Cookie Policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we may collect from you when you use SaveSense, the manners in which we may use such information, and the options and rights available to you. Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use available at www.SaveSense.com/terms (the "Terms"), which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference. 

#### 1\. Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)

BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING SAVESENSE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, ACCESS, OR USE SAVESENSE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER, AND PROMPTLY ERASE AND REMOVE SAVESENSE AND ANY PART THEREOF FROM YOUR SYSTEMS. Please note: you are not obligated by law to provide us with any Information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are providing us with Information at your own free will, for the purposes described in this privacy policy, and that we may retain such Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any applicable laws and regulations. 

#### 2\. Which information we may collect on our Users?

**We may collect two types of data and information from our Users:**  

a. The first type of information is non-personally identifiable information pertaining to a User, which may be made available or gathered via the User's use of SaveSense (“Non-personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from which the Non-personal Information was collected. Non-personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information and aggregated usage information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on SaveSense, type of operation system, User's 'click-stream' on SaveSense and/or any e-commerce websites operated by third parties (including Third Party Services, as such term is defined in the Terms) including but not limited to search queries and related searches on search engines, browser type, language and keyboard language, etc. 

b. The second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature (“Personal Information”). 

**Personal Information which is being gathered consists of the following:**  
The User's IP address or other persistent user identifier, which is automatically provided by the User and used mainly for enhancing the User's experience and for geolocation personalization and security purposes, as further detailed below; Any Personal Information provided voluntarily by the User via SaveSense, such as the User's e-mail address in order to be contacted, the User's answers to questions presented to the User through SaveSense, and/or other actions performed by the User in connection with SaveSense; and/or Personal Information regarding Users online activity when browsing e-commerce websites (including Third Party Services), including but not limited to search queries and related searches on search engines. For avoidance of doubt, any Non-personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists. We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and this Privacy Policy. 

#### 3\. How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?

**There are two main methods we use:**  

a. We collect information through your use of SaveSense. In other words, when you are using SaveSense, including when you use third-party e-commerce websites and services following the installation of SaveSense, we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed below. 

b. We collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, we collect Personal Information which you voluntarily provide when you contact us directly. We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below. 

#### 4\. What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?

We collect Non-personal and Personal Information in order to provide and operate SaveSense, including for statistical' security and research purposes; to enable us to further develop, customize and improve SaveSense based on Users common preferences and uses; and to enable us to provide our Users with a better user experience, with more relevant products, offers and deals and other marketing materials, and with technical assistance and support. 

#### 5\. Sharing Information with Third Parties

The Company will not share any Personal Information it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Company may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User's support requests; (e) to respond to claims that any content available on the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its Users, or the general public; (h) when the Company or any of its affiliates is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (i) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through the Company's authorized third party service providers (for example, Amazon Web Services), as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) to cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the User's experience. For avoidance of doubt, the Company may transfer and disclose to third parties or otherwise use Non-personal Information at its sole discretion. 

#### 6\. Deletion of Personal Information

If for any reason you wish us to delete your Personal Information stored with us and identifying to you, please send us an e-mail to: support@SaveSense.com and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws. Note that unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for a period of 12 months or a longer period as reasonably and legally required. 

#### 7\. Minors

To use SaveSense, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). The Company does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using SaveSense. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information' we cannot be responsible for the act of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that will prevent such access. If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with this privacy policy, please contact us directly at support@SaveSense.com and our privacy officer shall investigate promptly. 

#### 8\. Security

We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of SaveSense and the Site, and the User's Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on Amazon Web Services which provides advanced security features. The Company employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. However, we do not and cannot guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur. 

#### 9\. Third Party Software/Service

While using SaveSense we may be using third party software and/or service, in order to collect and/or process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics, which privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html; and Amazon Web Services which privacy policy can be found at: http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/. Third Party Services While using SaveSense you may encounter links to Third Party Content and/or Third Party Services, including through Offers and Deals available via SaveSense. Please be advised that such Third Party Services are independent from the Company, and if you click on any of these Offers and Deals, these Third Party Services may use cookies and other web-tracking technologies to collect non-personal and/or personal information about you. We assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such services. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such third parties, as their terms, not ours, will apply to any of your interactions with such third parties. 

#### 10\. Cookies

When you access or use SaveSense we use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer ("Local Storage") and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by SaveSense are created per session you launch when the application starts for the first time, and may persist until the application is removed from your computer. We do not include any information about you other than your session and anonymous globally unique identifier key, the date and time at which you have started using the application, information about how you have downloaded SaveSense to your computer and information necessary to serve you different content, such as when performing user-interface so-called “A/B tests". These cookies can be removed by using your browser’s cookie/Local Storage cleaning facilities. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage altogether. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer's hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited. The list below provides additional information regarding the types of cookies we use and their purpose: Functionality Cookies: used to identify you as an user and you preferences to provide you with customized offers and deals; we also use such cookies to label you as an opted-out user in case you will choose to opt out of our services; 

Analytics Cookies: used to collect information about how users use SaveSense. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve SaveSense. Such information is collected in an aggregated form, including the number of Users of SaveSense, where Users have access to SaveSense from and the webpages they visited. For these services we utilize Google Analytics services and you advised to http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ for an overview of privacy at Google; 

#### 11\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and at its sole discretion, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this Privacy Policy on the homepage of our Site and/or we will notify you via SaveSense regarding such changes. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on any of the abovementioned methods. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of SaveSense after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes. 

#### 12\. Have any Questions?

If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us an e-mail at: support@SaveSense.com and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
